《越狱》前情提要K
Previously on Prison Break:
金先生，莎拉丹奎迪 在我掌控之中
Mr. Kim. Sara Tancredi. I'm on it.
-你的时间该用来跟踪她吗？ -没错
- Pursuing her the best use of your time? - It is.
-我会通知总统 -我直接和总统联络
- I'll let the president know. - I contact the president.
由我和她连络
I'll contact her.
帕托西克没有家人？
No family with Patoshik?
-一点线索都没有？ -对
- Nothing? - Yeah,
四年前他杀光他的家人
Until about four years ago when he killed them.
（查尔斯帕托西克）
Fernando Sucre, He was in Las vegas around 2,
苏克约两点 出现在拉斯维加斯
跟包威和富兰克林一样在西部
out west. Just like Bagwell and Franklin.
认识迪比库柏吗？ 那笔钱在犹他州，他们全都要去
You know D.B. Cooper? The money's in Utah and they're all going to get it.
你是福克斯河州立监狱的逃犯之一
You're one of them Fox River boys,
-找到地图了吗？ -没有，有人拿走了
- Come on, you got the map? - No. Someone else does.
我把地图记在脑海里后才毁掉
Before I destroyed it, I committed it to my photographic memory.
我知道地点 你们则有体力
I have the information, you have the manual requirements necessary...
可以挖出威莫兰的钱财
...to unearth Westmoreland's buried booty.
-进去 -好啦
- Get in. - Okay.
肯定就在前方
Should be dead ahead.
浑蛋们在上面盖满房子
The bastards built over it.
地窖不见了
It's gone.
15分钟后就要开店了
We have to open up in 15 minutes.
-有什么关系？冒险一下 -我说不行
- So? That doesn't matter. I dare you. - I said no.
冒险一下，拜托
I dare you, please.
（犹他州，图尔）
牧场不见了，麦可
The ranch is gone, Michael.
但是五百万可能还在
Well, the five million might not be.
你要如何找那些钱？
And you're gonna find it how?
难道你的屁股有纹上卜问棒？
What, you got a divining rod tattooed on your ass?
除了你对地图 所谓的清晰记忆
I don't wanna hear anything from you...
其他的事我一概不想听
...other than what your photographic memory spits out regarding that map!
对我说话客气一点，小子
You watch your tone with me, boy.
我会把你丢在路边 自生自灭，小子
I will watch you get tossed to the side of the road to fend for yourself, boy.
因为你要是 不记得地窖的位置
Because if you can't remember where that silo was...
你对我们就毫无用处
...you're worthless to us.
-你们，放我出去 -闭嘴
- Yo, fools, let me out. - Shut up.
-地图 -好K
- The map! - Okay, okay. All right, all right, all right.
放我出去，老大
Let me out, boss.
牧场位于一个区块中间
The ranch was in the center of a box.
一旁是绵羊路 库库辛路和它垂直交叉
Sheep Road on one side, Kokosing Road perpendicular.
土地中央有间牧场房
In the center of the property was the ranch house...
房子旁边围绕着树木
...and the ranch house was surrounded by trees.
放我出去
Let me out.
这里每棵树都是刚种的
Every tree here is a year old at most...
除了那些之外
...except those.
地窖在哪里？
Where's the silo?
在树木内侧，应该是左方
Inside the trees, I wanna say on the left...
但那里可能有个谷仓
...but that may have been a barn.
各位，我已经尽力回想了 但我没料到这里
I remembered the best I could, gents, but I didn't know this place...
会盖满了房子
...would now be smothered in tract homes.
抱歉，我可没有天才的记忆
So, you know, I'm sorry that I'm not Rain Man over here.
（犹他州Q湖城，联邦大楼）
-亚历曼宏，你好 -莱尔山兹
- Alex Mahone. How are you? - Lyle sands.
我们已了解逃犯状况
We've been briefed on all the men at large.
Q湖城分局的所有人力资源
The full force and resources of the entire salt Lake City Field office...
都任你差遣
...are at your disposal.
谢谢，我方分局要的 迪比库柏档案准备好了吗？
Thank you. Do you have the files my office requested on D.B. Cooper?
现在正在调资料，是30年前 迪比库柏案的资料吗？
We're pulling them now. And this is the D.B. Cooper case from 30 years ago?
对，如果能马上给我资料 我会很感激
Correct. If I can get those files immediately, I'd appreciate it.
抱歉，你不是要来抓 福克斯河八人帮吗？
Sorry, but I have to ask. Aren't you here for the Fox River 8?
对，他们来犹他州 找迪比库柏的钱
I am. And they're here in Utah to get D.B. Cooper's money.
快给我档案好吗，莱尔？
So how about those files, Lyle?
-地窖K -这样做太蠢了
- Silo. Silo, silo. - This is stupid.
-我们会被抓到的 -闭嘴，我想起来了
- We're gonna get made out here. - All right, shut it. I think I remember.
如果要我打赌 我有把握地窖在房子左边
If I had to bet, I'd lay it all on the silo being on the left of the ranch house...
树的内侧
...inside the trees.
不对，是在树的外侧
No. It's outside the trees.
就在那边
Right there.
看见那两棵树了吗？ 它们比其他树矮
You see those two trees? They're shorter than the rest.
树木都是同时种植的 可是阳光比较难照到它们
They were all planted at the same time but those two didn't get as much sunlight.
有东西挡住了阳光
Something was in their way.
就是地窖
The silo.
我们的钱 应该就在那座车库下方
Our money should be right there, under that garage.
最好是对的，小子
You better be right, boy.
这里不是高级的分售土地
This isn't a high-end subdivision.
建商仓促拆掉原本的建筑
They slapped this place up overnight.
地窖的地基可能还在
The silo's foundations might still be there.
为了省钱 建商应该只是在地基上
To save money, they probably just laid the concrete...
铺了水泥当作车库地板
...for the garage floor right on top of it.
我们往下挖，挖到地基就留下 没有的话就离开
We'll dig straight down. If we hit the foundation, we stay. If not, we go.
动手吧
Let's do it.
可恶
Oh, man.
拿螺丝起子杀了她 就没问题了
Ain't no problem that a screwdriver to her temple won't fix.
片名：越狱风云
剧名：一块地之谜
人死是很正常的事，两位
People die all the time, boys.
五百万却是可遇不可求
Five million dollars comes once in a lifetime.
-让我出来，你们别这样 -我们得想个办法
- Let me out of here, man. Come on, guys. - Well, we gotta do something.
不要伤害任何人
And it's not gonna involve hurting anyone.
我有办法了
I got an idea.
首先我们需要些工具
First, we're gonna need some supplies.
我绝对不同意
A hundred and 10 percent, I do not agree with this.
想要成事就得靠所有人出力
Everybody's gotta pitch in to make this happen.
但狱中的经验显示 不能相信那小伙子
But back in the big house, the boy proved he couldn't be trusted.
所以我们才在外面下手
Which is why we're doing it here.
如果他在镇上被抓到 也不知道屋子在哪
If he gets caught in town, he ain't got a clue where the house is.
而且不能背叛的人是你
Besides, you're the one we can't turn our backs on.
老兄，我差点死掉
I could have died in there, man.
你猜怎么着？我需要你的帮忙
Well, guess what. I need you to do something.
你先帮我一个忙 我也要分一份钱
I need you to do something for me. I want my cut of the money.
等你证明我们可以信任你 一切好谈
Well, we'll talk once you prove we can trust you.
要我做什么？
What do I gotta do?
我要你回去那间园艺店 把清单上的东西拿来
I want you to go back to that garden center and get everything on this list.
还有替车子加油
And gas up the car.
一小时后回来这里找我们
And we'll meet you right back here in an hour.
-好 -大卫
- All right. - And, David...
不要搞砸了
...don't screw this up.
这里不是福克斯河监狱
This ain't Fox River no more, man.
在外面我才是真正的高手
You're looking at the real deal now.
但是我要分一份钱
But I want my cut.
一小时后我就回来
Be back in an hour.
我们走吧
Let's go.
你们错了
Mistake.
大错特错
Big mistake.
（犹他州北部，36号公路）
真是的
Oh, come on, now.
我真高兴见到你
Am I glad to see you.
你徒步来这里？
You walk here?
不，说来话长
No, it's just a long story, man.
你不是要去和家人团聚吗？
I thought you were meeting up with your family.
我在途中遇到了一些阻碍，你呢？
I met a few roadblocks. And you?
我也是
Yeah.
我猜猜，你要去图尔
Well, let me guess. You're going to Tooele.
对
Yeah.
看来我们要去同一个地点
Well, looks like we're going the same direction.
希望我们来得不会太迟
Hopefully, we're not too late.
可以让我搭便车吗？
Can I hitch a ride?
听我说K
Hey, look...
帮助我绝对是值得的
...I'll make it worth your while.
（FBI分局 伊利诺州芝加哥）
We've got some good news, sir.
有好消息，长官
首次有帕托西克的消息
We got our first tip on Patoshik.
有人目击他出现在威斯康辛州 细得格罗夫的一家汉堡店
Spotted at a burger joint in Cedar Grove, Wisconsin.
先交给当地警方调查
Hand it over to local authorities for now.
今天只调查犹他州 和迪比库柏
The only thing we're working today is Utah and D.B. Cooper.
知道了
Got it.
莱尔
Lyle.
纪录上有个人 拥有唯一一张迪比库柏的钞票
There's a guy listed as having the only D.B. Cooper bill ever found.
-哈洛杰金斯 -对
- Harold Jenkins. - Yeah.
对，迪比在抢劫当天
D.B. Bought gas from Jenkins...
用一百元向杰金斯买汽油
...with a hundred on the day of the hijacking.
我们查过序号，是符合的
We checked the serial numbers and they matched.
这是你承办的案子？
You worked the case?
我当时刚毕业，至今无人能破案
Fresh out of the academy and nobody's cracked it yet.
你为何认为 这些逃犯知道钱藏在哪里？
What makes you think that these escapees know where the money is?
因为他们可能和真的 迪比库柏当过狱友
Because they may have been locked up with the real D.B. Cooper.
加油站的杰金斯还活着吗？
Jenkins from the gas station, he still alive?
应该是，当时他才18岁
Should be. He was only 18 at the time.
我们去找他吧
Well, let's go say hi to him.
（伊利诺州，芝加哥）
（786-369-6468）
抱歉，此号码无法拨通
We're sorry, that call cannot be completed as dialed,
请查明后再试
Please check the number and dial again,
（786-369-6468 736-339-8687）
莎拉丹奎迪有新消息吗？ 这应该是你来的原因吧
Do you have updates on sara Tancredi? I assume that's why you're here.
（华盛顿）
Yes.
对
Scofield sent her a message through the mail.
史柯菲传讯息给她
一个电话号码，不过是空号
A phone number that was disconnected.
老实说K
You know, to be honest...
我以为我是来向总统呈报
...I was expecting to brief the president.
好，关于这件事
Yeah, about that.
你应该能理解 卡洛琳现在很忙
Right now, as you can imagine, Caroline's quite busy.
她一向都很忙 我在她身边工作15年了
She's always been busy. I've been working with her for 15 years.
保罗K
Paul...
她现在是美国总统
...she's the president of the Unites states now.
对，是比尔和我帮她升官的
Yes, Bill and I helped to put her there.
如果你希望她继续执政
Well, if you'd like for her to remain in office...
我建议你现在开始行事低调
...you'll take my advice and just stay on the sidelines for now.
她现在不能和林克柏劳 牵扯上任何一丝关系
She needs to be completely insulated from anything regarding Lincoln Burrows.
我要见她
I wanna talk to her.
现在你只能向我一个人呈报
You report to me now, and only me.
在我批准前不准联络卡洛琳
Don't try and contact Caroline again without my approval...
你也不能说来就来
...and don't show up here unannounced.
完成你的任务，找到柏劳
Finish the job you were given. Get Burrows.
你说透过莎拉丹奎迪能找到他 就不计代价K
If you're telling me the road to him leads through sara Tancredi, by all means...
把他找出来吧
...pursue it.
等你完成任务 人们淡忘这件事后
And once that's been accomplished and this whole thing goes away...
我们会再把你 调回卡洛琳的身边
...we'll go about transitioning you back into Caroline's life.
莎拉身上还有其他消息吗？
Now, do you have anything else on sara?
总统对你坚信不移
The president has unwavering faith in you.
她要你亲自眼见参议院
She wants you to go through senate approval...
审核的过程
...with your eyes wide open.
有谁对我们不利？ 国会和参议院有关键同盟
- So what are we up against? - Key allies in the House and senate...
包括梅尔霍夫 邦威尔和桑莫维尔
...are Meyerhoff, Barnwell and sommerville.
-他们有可能会投靠我方 -有谁反对？
- Counting on them to sway the middle. - Who's the opposition?
布雷克和克罗伦参议员 口头反对
Senators Blake and Killoren have openly vocalized...
你当副总统
...their opposition to you as VP.
他们有提出原因吗？
Any indication as to why?
政治报复，因为总统 上个月同意能源法案
Political payback for the president's vote on the energy bill last month.
他们很惊讶 而他们不喜欢出奇不意
Took them by surprise and they don't like surprises.
爸K兰斯 这位是我的父亲弗兰克
- Dad. Lance, this is my father, Frank. - Pleasure to meet you, sir.
很高兴认识你
没什么好担心的
It's nothing to lose sleep over.
老实说，现在最严重的问题
Frankly, the biggest issue we have to address...
只有令嫒可能面临的刑责
...are the charges facing your daughter.
州长，你有听到吗？
Governor, are you with me?
当然
Absolutely.
（伍德园艺行）
你安静点，好吗？
Yo, just chill, dog. Listen...
等我完事，离开这里 我们会通报，就会有人来救你
...once we roll out, we bounce out of town, we'll drop a dime and they'll find you.
安静点，老兄
Just be quiet. Just chill, man.
伍德？
Woody?
你在哪？伍德
Where you at? Woody?
我找威廉斯警长
I need sheriff Williams.
好，我在线上等
Yeah, I'll hold.
伍德？
Woody?
你怎么会懂电工的事？
Where'd you learn about electricity?
我以前会从变电箱偷裸铜线
I used to steal copper wiring from transformer boxes.
然后拿去码头卖掉，赚点小钱
Then I'd sell them on the docks, make a few bucks.
你当时都在学校
You were in school, of course.
我只是看看而已，帅哥
I was just looking, pretty. What's that old chestnut?
看看菜单不代表我会吃
I can look at the menu, doesn't mean I'm gonna eat.
我们进去拿钱，之后就离开
We get in, we get the money, we get out.
-仅此而已 -那当然
- That's it. - No, absolutely.
成功了
We're good.
现在都要靠那小子了
Now, it's just up to the kid.
-东西都拿了吗？ -拿了K
- Did you get everything? - Yeah. Yeah, I got it.
-怎么了？ -没事，我解决了
- What? - Nothing. It's cool. I handled it.
-怎么了？ -好啦，我说
- What? - Whoa. Okay.
听好，有个家伙来店里
Check it. This fool came in the shop.
他怪怪的，发现事态不对劲
He was acting all shady, he got a bad vibe...
然后他拿起手机打电话 所以我打了他
...so he picked up his cellie phone, he started to make a call, so I popped him.
-什么？ -我用铲子打他
- What?! - I hit him with the shovel, man.
我不知道能怎么办
I didn't know what else to do.
我把他绑起来 把他跟那乡巴佬关在一起
I tied him up and I put him in the back room with that other country hick.
-你们看吧K -至少我成功了，娘娘腔
- Here we go. Here we go. - I came through, you gimp.
-他打电话给谁？ -警长
- Who was he calling? - The sheriff.
我不知道，老兄 事情发生得太快了
Man, I don't know, dude. It just set off so quick.
-电话有打通吗？ -也许，我不知道
- Did the call go through? - Maybe, man. I don't know.
也许？他有打通吗？
Maybe? Did the call go through?
有，不K我也不知道 我不知道
Yes, l... No, I don't know. I don't know, man.
可是我把东西拿来了
Yo, but I got the gear.
我们得快点行动
We gotta move on this now.
有事吗？
Yes?
抱歉打扰了，女士 你家有停电吗？
Sorry to bother you, ma'am. Is your electricity out?
不好意思，我要找哈洛杰金斯
Excuse me. I'm looking for a Harold Jenkins.
我就是
Right here.
我是亚历山大曼宏 调查局
Alexander Mahone, FBI.
我已经远离她50尺了
I'm staying 50 feet away from her at all times.
她到底还想怎样？
What the hell else does she want?
这不是我找你的原因
I'm not here about that.
-那是什么事？ -迪比库柏
- What are you here for? - D.B. Cooper.
还有人在调查这家伙？
People still wanna know about that guy?
真难以置信
Unbelievable.
你在他去过的 美国福克加油站工作过
You worked the gas station in American Fork where he filled up.
对，他看起来很平常 几乎没有说话
Yeah. Normal-Iooking guy. Barely said a word.
你30年前做的笔录 内容有些不一致
There were some discrepancies in the statement you filed 30 years ago.
你在笔录中指出 他在早上七点来加油
In the report, it's noted that you said he filled up at 7 a. M...
之后你又说是晚上七点
...but on another occasion, you said it was 7 p.m.
-哪一个才对？ -都对
- Which was it? - Both.
他来加油两次？
He gassed up twice?
对
Yeah.
两次都把油加满？
Full tanks both times?
对，怎么了？
Yeah. Why?
系统什么？
A systems what?
系统诊断测试
It's a systems diagnostics test.
我们的查询系统已经找到
Footage from our gopher cam picked up exactly...
你的线路故障点
...where your line was corrupted.
是谁弄坏的？
And who corrupted it?
-你们吗？ -有可能
- You guys? - Maybe.
我只知道我的上司要我
All I know is my supervisor called and said he wants me and my crew...
和组员过来这里 立即修复问题
...to get over here and fix that problem double quick, double time.
-所以你们不是电力公司的人？ -不是，女士
- So you're not with the electric company? - No, ma'am.
你尽管通知你的公司
Now, feel free to call your company.
不过我告诉你 他们只会派技术人员来
But I tell you, all they'll do is send over some tech.
幸运的话，明天才会来
Maybe tomorrow, if you're lucky.
他会花一整天找出故障点
And he'll spend a whole day trying to find the problem...
再花一天修理
...and another day trying to fix it.
不过我们已经来了
But we're here right now.
你可以马上回去打果汁
And we're ready to turn your juice back on.
果汁？
My juice?
没错
That's right.
那么K
And...
他们是你的组员？
...that's your crew?
是的，女士
Yes, ma'am.
迪比库柏的车 是1965年的雪佛兰新星
Yeah, D.B. Cooper was driving a 1965 Chevy Nova.
库柏没有持有车辆的纪录
There's no record on file that Cooper even had a car.
可是查理威莫兰有车子 他当时登记的车
But Charles Westmoreland did and the car registered to him...
是1965年的雪佛兰新星 油箱可装16加仑
...at the time was a 1965 Chevy Nova with a 16-gallon gas tank.
当时雪佛兰那样的车 一加仑约可跑八里
Back then, a Chevy that size got approximately eight miles to the gallon.
迪比库柏在美国福克加油站停下 早上先加一次油
D.B. Stopped at the station in American Fork and gassed up once early that day...
同一天晚上又回来再加油
...and then came back later that same night and gassed up again.
一个要直接 往南到墨西哥的人
Now, why would a guy headed to Mexico, which is a straight shot south,,,
为何会花一整天偏离路线绕路？
,,, drive off the main road for an all-day detour?
-为了钱 -没错
- The money. - Exactly.
库柏，就是威莫兰 带着五百万元跳机
Cooper, Westmoreland, jumped out of a plane with $5 million.
不过威莫兰 被逮捕时身上没有钱
But Westmoreland didn't have the money on him when he was arrested.
他被捕前就把钱藏了起来 把麦克笔给我
He ditched it before he got caught. Give me that magic marker.
以美国福克为中心 他不可能去了
From American Fork, he couldn't have gone further...
超过方圆64里的地区
...than 64 miles in any direction.
去查这地区内所有的消息
I want everything you've got in that perimeter.
这些逃犯就在其中一个小镇里
Those cons are in one of these towns...
就算是猫失踪的小事 也要通知我
...and if there's so much as a cat missing in one of them, I wanna know about it.
故障的线路正好通过你家车库下
The defective cable runs right beneath your garage.
我们得挖开地板才能修理线路
We're gonna have to dig up the floor to get to it.
谁会赔偿这些费用？
Well, who's gonna pay for this...
还有清理和修理费怎么办？
...and what about the cleanup and the repair?
我们公司会负担所有费用
Well, the company will cover all costs.
我们只会挖个小沟槽
We'll just dig a small trench.
完工后，我们会再铺上水泥 看起来跟新的一样
Once we're finished, we'll re-lay the cement. It'll look as good as new.
要花多久时间？
How long is it gonna take?
无论如何，今天一定能完工
One way or another, we'll be out of here today.
我们该快点开工了，女士
Really need to get started, ma'am.
我们不希望让你这种美人
Wouldn't want a pretty little thing like yourself sitting...
今晚坐在黑暗中，对吧？
...in the dark tonight, now, would we?
那要看我旁边坐的是谁
Well, that depends on who I'm sitting with.
说得对
Touche.
好吧，你们动工 做你们要做的事吧
Fine. It's okay, y'all go ahead and do whatever y'all need to do.
珍娜，施工的噪音不小
Jeanette, the noise might be substantial.
你去打网球可能会好一点
You might wanna take in that tennis game after all.
不了K现在打球太热了
Oh, no, it's too hot for that now.
何况我要盯紧你们所有人 你们才不会偷东西
Plus, I gotta keep an eye on you all and make sure you don't steal anything.
女士
Ma'am.
-你好吗？ -很好
- How are you? - Good.
好，中间人呢？
All right, where's Tweener?
他在隔壁插延长线
He's next door plugging in the extension cord.
-我们得挖开水泥 -各位，有人来了
- We're gonna have to cut up the cement. - Yo, we gots company.
你好吗，小白脸？
What's up, snowflake?
你还是一如往昔 时机抓得恰到好处
Well, as always, your timing is flawless.
-我不懂你的意思 -让我解释给你听
- I don't follow. - Well, let me try to explain it to you.
现在我们在试图施工
We're trying to run something here...
不能让人随便进来
...and we can't have people walking in off the street.
是吗？你要我们离开 之后再寄支票给我们？
Oh, okay, so you want us to leave and then you can just mail us the check?
苏克，你信任我的
Sucre, I know you trust me...
你知道我会把钱分给你
...and you know I'll cut you in on that money.
可是现在你们俩会破坏一切
But the two of you being here right now jeopardizes everything.
我哪里也不去
I'm not going nowhere.
我要我那一份钱
I want my share of the money.
等等，老兄 这情况也不是第一次了吧？
Wait a minute, hold on, man. Ain't we did this dance before?
我说我要加入，你拒绝我
You know, I say I want in, you say no...
然后我威胁 要张扬你的勾当
...then I threaten to tell somebody about what's going on here.
接着你决定和平相处 我们就是和乐融融的一家人
And then you decide to play nice and then we're one big happy family.
我们别浪费时间了，好吗？
Why don't we just stop wasting time, all right?
谢谢
Thank you.
天啊，你还活着？
Damn, man, you still alive?
而且生龙活虎，小子
And kicking, homeboy.
你们怎么找到我们的？
How'd you find us?
如果我可以替美军 做全球卫星
Man, if I can do rapid deployment of satellite communications...
通讯网路连线的话K
...for Uncle sam all over the world...
情况如何？
How are you guys doing?
你是谁？他们是谁？
Who are you? Who are they?
我打了通电话给上司
I had to call my supervisor.
他多派人过来 这件事要尽快完工
He sent them right over. This job is a top priority.
公司希望尽快 有效率地修复线路
They want to get this done as quickly and as efficiently as possible.
珍娜，如我说过 我们有很多事要忙
Well, Jeanette, like I said, there's a lot of work to do...
而且噪音会很大
...and it's gonna be noisy.
我忘了问你们要喝什么
Oh, drinks. I forgot to ask.
不用了，谢谢
We're good. Thanks.
情况不妙
Yo, man, this is not good.
她随时会闯进来查看我们
We got her up in our grill checking in on us all the time.
这小子说得对
The boy is right.
既然我不能挖，我自愿去缠住她
And since I can't dig, I'll volunteer to keep her occupied.
不准碰她
You don't touch her.
难道你是修女不成？
Who are you, sister Mary Francis?
我知道怎么讨好女人
I know how to play nice.
我会盯着你的
I'll be watching.
（威斯康辛州，细得格罗夫）
比利？是你吗？
Billy? Is that you?
Billy, is that you?
对
Yeah.
真是感谢你
Thank you kindly.
说吧，你怎么不用工作？
Well, now, how did you get out of working?
是工会的规定
Union rules.
一定要有一名组员监督
One crew member always has to supervise.
我待会再去检查状况
I'll check on them in a bit.
柠檬汁？
Lemonade?
还要冰块吗？
Little more ice?
好
Yeah.
我喜欢添加一点K活力
And I like mine with a little oomph.
既然你现在正在工作
But since you're on the clock...
你应该不能陪我喝吧？
...I guess you can't join me?
加一点就好
Just two fingers.
好
All right.
好久没喝了
It's been a while.
是吗？
Yeah?
威士忌总是让我感到K暴戾
Whiskey always makes me feel irascible.
我不懂那是什么意思
I don't know what that means.
可是听起来很有趣
But I do like the sound of it.
你擦的香水是“天使”吗？
Are you wearing Angel perfume?
没错
I am.
我猜它让你想起前妻吧？
That reminds you of an ex, I take it.
对
Yeah.
是好的回忆K
Now, is that good memories...
还是坏的回忆？
...or bad memories?
都有
Both.
你有找到犸丽吗？
Did you talk to Maricruz?
我不想谈她的事
I don't wanna talk about her.
我得去喝杯水
I gotta get some water or something.
去房子另一边的水龙头喝水
Use the hose on the other side of the house.
苏克K
Sucre...
之后如果你遇到麻烦 上欧洲金翅网站
...down the road, if you're in trouble, Europeangoldfinch. Net.
我们可以上网联络
It's what we can all use to communicate.
到留言版留言
Post a note on the message board.
-网站叫什么？ -欧洲金翅网站
- What's it called? - Europeangoldfinch. Net.
那是一种鸟，对吧？
That's a bird, right?
我挖到东西了
I got something.
-是地窖的地基 -太好了
- It's the silo's foundation. - Hells, yeah.
谢谢你，查理
Thank you, Charles.
我们只要找到边缘，然后往下挖
We just need to find the edge and dig underneath it.
找到钱后就上路
We'll get the money, hit the back roads.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
我们得去先去图尔加油
We got to stop in Tooele first and gas up our ride.
你不是已经加了吗？
I thought you already did that.
园艺店的状况发生后 我就忘了，好吗？
Man, when the garden center thing happened, I just forgot, all right?
我要你回镇上
I want you to go back into town.
我要你把车子的油加满
I want you to gas up that car...
因为我不要带着上百万到处跑
...because I'm not driving around with millions of dollars in the trunk.
-听懂了吗？ -为何要我去？
- Do you understand? - Man, why do I got to do it?
-照做 -好啦
Okay.
好啦
我最好去看看我们的朋友
I better check in on our friend.
你真会这一招
You got it all the time.
扭来扭去的
Miss Tinsel toes.
比利？
Billy?
比利
什么事？
Yeah?
我帮你做了三明治
I made you a sandwich.
花生酱加果酱，面包边切掉
Peanut butter and jelly with the crusts cut off.
照你喜欢的做
Just like you like.
我真高兴你回来了
I'm so glad you came back.
我不想在你的伤口上洒Q 可是那个女孩真的不适合你
I don't wanna say I told you so, but that was just not the girl for you.
那是哪里？
Where is that?
你说哪里，甜心？
Where's what, sweetheart?
那幅划
That painting.
那是荷兰，我的出身地，你知道的
It's Holland, where I grew up. You know that.
-好漂亮 -那里最好了
- It's beautiful. - Oh, there's no place better.
如此宁静K
It's so peaceful...
让人忘却这个喧扰的世界
...so protected from this crazy world.
-接线生 -接线生你好
- Operator, - Hello, operator.
有人闯进我家里
There's an intruder in my house.
女士？你还在吗？
Hello, ma'am? Ma'am, are you there?
有人在吗？
Is anyone there?
听说图尔今天有些状况
Heard you had some activity in Tooele today.
没错，不过没必要惊动调查局吧？
A bit. Don't see how it warrants a visit from the FBI.
一名在圣路易念书女子的车
A stolen car was dumped outside of town...
在镇外被发现
...belonging to a woman from st. Louis.
-我说得对吗？ -没错
- Am I getting that right? - Yes, sir.
还有这里 店老板的女友通报他失踪
And then here, the owner's girlfriend reports him missing...
接着他的朋友过来找他 也跟着失踪
...and then his buddy comes by to check it out and he goes missing too.
对，伍德和查特每次一有机会
Woody and Chet have been known to drop everything...
就会丢下一切跑去猎野猪
...and go boar hunting when the opportunity arises.
他们也不会事先告诉母亲
And they don't tell their old ladies.
曼宏先生，我用午餐钱和你打赌 这里一切安好
Mr. Mahone, I'll bet you my lunch money there's nothing amiss around here.
他父亲马上会把钥匙送来 到时你可以自己去看
His dad will be showing up soon with the keys and you can look for yourself.
等等，你要做什么？
Whoa, what are you doing?
曼宏先生
Mr. Mahone.
他们在这里 那些逃犯，他们在镇上
They're here. Those escaped convicts. They're here in town.
谁在那里？
Who's there?
我们是警察，女士 你没事吧？
It's the police, ma'am. You okay?
没事
Yes.
-麻烦你告诉我们发生了什么事 -有一个怪男人
- Can you tell me what happened? - There was this strange man.
我做了花生酱 加果酱的三明治给他
I made him a peanut butter and jelly sandwich.
我以为他是比利
I thought he was Billy.
等孩子们上床睡觉，我们会一起洗澡
And once the kids went to sleep, we'd take a bath.
慢慢地洗个澡
A long bath.
之后我会坐在那 看着她做保养的例行公事
And afterwards, I'd just sit there and watch her do her routine.
她会擦乳液，梳头发
She'd rub her lotion on, comb her hair...
再换上睡衣
...dress up in her nighttime fineries.
听得我心痒痒
Oh, you're killing me.
她的脖子有个部份，就在这里
She had this spot on her neck right here.
每次都会让她兴奋
Gave her goose bumps every time.
还有香水味
And that perfume...
我的前夫是会计师
My ex, he was an accountant.
他真的很拘谨
He was really buttoned up.
每次房事都草草了事
It was wham, bam, thank you, sam.
他真是不应该
Well, shame on him.
你为何和那个女人分开？
Why did it end with that lady you were talking about?
我们分道扬镖罢了
Just went our separate ways.
我心中最佳的心碎良药是什么 你知道吗？
Do you know what I think the best cure is for a broken heart?
快告诉我
Do tell.
回到单车上
Get back on the bike.
什么样的单车不重要
Whatever bike it is.
说得太好了
Amen to that.
聊到这里
Speaking of...
帮我个忙好吗？
...could you do something for me?
当然好
I'm certain of it.
过来
Come here.
不过你要非常慎重
Only, you have to be very discreet.
不会比我更慎重了
They don't come any discreeter.
你知道那个高大的家伙？
You know that big guy?
那个魁梧、话不多的家伙？
The strong guy that doesn't speak much?
你可以帮我问他
Would you go in there...
愿意和我去喝一杯吗？
...and ask him if he would like to have a drink with me...
就是下班后
...after he punches out?
拜托你了
Please.
你刚刚一直在耍我对吧？
You've just been playing me this whole time, haven't you?
别这样
Come on.
别这么想
Don't be like that.
帮我问你的朋友好吗？
Would you just go in and ask your friend?
拜托
Please.
（伊利诺州，芝加哥）
-爸 -莎拉，我一直在找你
- Hey, Dad. - Sara, I've been trying to reach you.
我今天一直和 我的辩护律师在一起
Uh, yeah, I've been meeting with my defense attorneys all day.
-你在华盛顿吗？ -对，但我会
- You in Washington? - Yeah, I'm coming back...
搭下班飞机回去
...on the next flight.
-你不是要待一阵子吗？ -不，行程变了
- I thought you're gonna be there for a while. - No, plan's changed.
莎拉，记得我去找你时 和你在一起的那个男人吗？
Sara, you remember that guy that I met with you in your apartment?
我要你离他远一点
I want you to stay away from him.
你是说戒毒会的兰斯？
Who, Lance from my group?
对，就是他 他的身份是假的
Yeah, yeah, that's him. He is not who he says he is.
我还发现了其他事
I found out some other things too,
-你在说什么？ -你是对的
- What are you talking about? - You were right,
-莎拉？ -我得挂电话了
- Sara? - I gotta go.
对，没错
Yeah, that's right.
对
Yeah.
-你好 -马上好，先生
- Yo. - Just one second, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
-有事能效劳吗？ -三号加四十元
- Can I help you? - Just put 40 on three.
抱歉，你说几号机？
I'm sorry, what pump was that?
-三号 -那台塞住了
- Three. - That one's been sticking.
-那我把车移一下 -不，不用麻烦
- Okay. Then, I'll move the car. - No. No, don't trouble yourself.
我请技工出来帮你加油
I'll have the mechanic come out and pump it for you.
三号机有顾客
I've got a customer waiting on three.
-好，马上来 -听着，我在赶时间
- All right, I'll be right there. - I'm in a hurry, all right?
他马上就会出来
Oh, he'll be right out. Just one second.
双手抱头，跪下
Put your hands behind your head and drop to your knees.
-天啊 -跪下
- Oh, God. - Drop!
他们在哪里？
Where are they?
什么K？
What? What?
其他人在哪里？
Where are they?
不管他是否只有一只手 我认为乡巴佬也该帮忙挖
Hey, man, one hand or not, I think hillbilly needs to be up in here digging.
你觉得呢？
What you think?
好
Good man.
你跑上来干嘛？
What the hell are you doing up here?
很抱歉，珍娜
I'm sorry, Jeanette.
我在楼下没见到你，又听到怪声
I just didn't see you downstairs. I heard something.
-很抱歉我闯进来 -别费心了
- I apologize for barging in. - Don't bother.
她喜欢的是身材魁梧的家伙
She's got the hots for the big strong one.
抱歉，珍娜 我们要回去工作了
I'm sorry, Jeanette. We're gonna get back to work now.
不，我认为你们完工了
No, I think y'all are done.
我认为你们该走了
And I think y'all need to leave now.
我们快修好了
We're almost finished.
不，我认为已经修好了 我要你们现在离开我的房子
No, I think you are finished, okay? And I want you to leave my house now.
苏克，去看看
Sucre, check it out.
警察
Cop.
感谢老天
Oh, thank God.
-你要上哪去？ -茶包，放开她！
- Where you going? - T-Bag, let her go!
天啊
Oh, God.
她是我们解套的唯一救星，帅哥
She's our only way out of this, pretty.
不准发出声音，你这老女人 否则我割断你的喉咙
Don't say a word, you old whore, or I'm gonna cut your throat out.